Grafitti Markup Language
my name is Evan dfdfd
fI am an artist and I'm going to talk about grafitti markup languagefdfd
my work happens between open source and popular culture
how to make open source interchange with popular culture
we also do a project called LaserTag, an open source software for grafitti writters
and the main thing I'm trying to come up with grafitti reasearch work is that
combining contagious media like viral media and things that get popular on the web
with source code is a good way to spread free culture
into communities that aren't used to hearing about that
so, the new project I'm talking about is the same idea only combining open data with popular culture
and how to make that popular and interesting, all right?
another software, open source project isabout capturing grafitti data
and saving that digitally in a way that can be transfered easily between people
and creates visuallizations
the application also exports this files in the grafitti markup language
which is meant to be a very accessible format
easy for hobbyist programmers and is essentially an XML file
with x, y and time coordinates
and there's also an online database
that's an open database that uploads and downloads GML files
so you can upload a GML... download a GML...
and programmers can get involved by making applications
so, things I've made with GML...
this is an application that takes in GML file, creates 3D data, and exports STL files
which you can then import into Blender
and send it to 3d-printers
so, I was making 3d prints of some grafitti data
another project...
it's eye-writter, another project that uses GML
it's designed for a grafitti writer who may not move but his eyes
and so he can write grafitti with his eyes
this is open source software
and this software, like other software, also exports in the same file format
and so these applications can now talk to each other and
developers are taking that data and doing interesting things
this is one taking GML file and using it to write to a robot
this is the same GML data used by an artist who is creating art with ping pong
it's just a different robot
online people are writting web-based applications
this is one in processing,
there's a canvas player, there's an SVG player
Toby is working on a web marker app that takes in GML
and uses the open database so you can write tags in webpages
and so it's all about usefulness of having an open standard
and having different open source input devices, different open source export devices
but in the center is just an open data format and an online database that is completely open
and it is all about getting computer hackers and grafitti writers
hanging out more, talking more, making new projects
and about getting open source spread to new communities
so getting this into places with people who might not be in a tech circles
people that might now be in grafitti circles
but this idea of hacking whether it is in the city or whether it is in code
and getting this people sort of making projects together
so it is using grafitti as a way to sort of spread free culture into popular culture
and that's the big fish
kjkkkk
lkkjkjk
kjkj
jkj'
fdsfjkjkj
kjkjfdkj
kjkjfdsafdkj
kjkjkfafadfj
kjkjkdfdfdafddaffj
fasfdfdakjkjkj
kjkjkfdfadfaj
fdfadfakjkjk
fdsfadfadfkjkjk
fdsfdasfkjkjk
fdsfdafkjkjk
fdafdfkjkjk
kjkj  as fdsfa
dsfakjkj          fsadf
kjkjfdafadf
fdfddakjkj
fdafddkjkj
dfafdsfkjkj
fdfadfkjkj
dfafdsafkjkj