Don't show this text it may be used to insert hidden asdfasdfasdfasdfasdf
SubRipasdf
This text should be black
If you see this with the normal font, the player don't support font face
Hidden
This text should be small
This text should be normal
This text should be big
This should be an E with an accent: È
日本語
This text should be bold, italics and underline
This text should be small and green
This text should be small and red
This text should be big and brown
This line should be bold
This line should be italics
This line should be underline
This line should be strikethrough
Both lines
should be underlined
It would be a good thing to
hide invalid html tags that are closed and show the text in them
but show un-closed invalid html tags
and also
hide invalid html tags with parameters that are closed and show the text in them
but show un-closed invalid html tags
This text should be showed underlined without problems also: 21,4
This shouldn't be underlined
This text should be in the normal position...
Implementation is the same of the ASS tag
This text should be at the
top and horizontally centered
middle and horizontally centered
This text should be at the
bottom and horizontally centered
top and horizontally at the left
This text should be at the
middle and horizontally at the left
bottom and horizontally at the left
This text should be at the
top and horizontally at the right
middle and horizontally at the right
This text should be at the
bottom and horizontally at the right
This could be the most difficult thing to implement
First text
Second, it shouldn't overlap first
Third, it should replace second
Fourth, it shouldn't overlap first and third
Fifth, it should replace third
Sixth, it shouldn't be
showed overlapped
TEXT 1 (bottom)
text 2
Hide these tags:
also hide these tags:
but show this:
\h\h\h\h\hA (5 hard spaces followed by a letter)
A (No hard spaces followed by a letter)
\h\h\h\h\hA (05 hard spaces followed by a letter)
05 hard spaces between letters: A\h\h\h\h\hA
05 spaces between letters: A     A
A letter followed by 5 hard spaces: A\h\h\h\h\h
A letter followed by no hard spaces: A
\N^--Hard line break
new one